[instrumental music]
That's like the tenth time
I've peed since I've been here.
That's also like
the tenth time you've told us.
Yeah, oh, I'm sorry,
it must be really hard to hear.
I tell ya, it's a lot easier
having three babies playing
"Bring in 'da noise, Bring in
'da Funk" on your bladder!
I'm so sick
of being pregnant.
The only happiness I get
is from a cup of coffee
which of course is decaf,
'cause, "Oh, I'm pregnant!"
Pheebs, you-you want a cookie?
Thank you so much.
So, uh, Pheebs, honey, how are
those mood swings comin'?
I haven't really had any yet.
[theme song]
♪ So no one told you life
was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're
always stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day
your week your month ♪
♪ Or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me too ♪♪
[instrumental music]
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Alright, here's the ring.
[gasps]
Yes! Yes!
A thousand times yes!
So, uh, any ideas
for the bachelor party yet?
Whoa-whoa-whoa! Before you
start handing out wedding rings
and planning bachelor parties,
don't you have
to decide who your
best man is gonna be?
Oh, it's awkward.
It's awkward. It's awkward.
I sort of already
asked Chandler.
What? He got to do it
at your first wedding.
Joey, I figured
you'd understand.
I mean, I-I've known him
a lot longer.
Come on, Ross! Look, I-I don't
have any brothers.
I'm never gonna get
to be a best man!
You can be the best man
when I get married.
I'm never gonna get
to be a best man!
Wait-wait, so, you get
to be my best man twice
and I don't get to be
yours at all?
Oh, no, you.. Yeah, of course,
you can be my best man.
What about me?
You-you just said I could!
I'm not even getting married!
Okay, this is a question
for science fiction writers.
I can't believe
you're not picking me.
Hey, how could it not be me?
I'm not even.. I'm not even..
Alright, you know what,
that's it.
From now on, Joey,
I want you to be my best man.
Yes!
Shame about you though, man.
[instrumental music]
- Stop it.
- What?
One of the babies is kicking.
I thought that was a good thing.
It's not kicking me,
it's kicking
one of the other babies.
Oh! Don't make me
come in there!
- Hey.
- (Monica) Hey.
Do you guys have like
a big bowl I can borrow?
Yeah, there's one right
under the cabinet.
- Thanks.
- Why do you need it?
Oh, we're having a big party
tomorrow night. Later!
(Rachel)
'Whoa! Hey-hey'
you planning on inviting us?
No-o-o, no. Later.
Hey! Get your ass
back here, Tribbiani!
Hormones.
What Phoebe meant
to say was, um
how come you're having a party
and we're not invited?
Oh, it's Ross' bachelor party.
So?
Are you bachelors?
- No.
- Are you strippers?
- Then you're not invited.
Alright, fine!
You're not invited
to, uh, the party that
we're gonna have either.
Oh, wh-what party?
Well, um..
The baby shower
for Phoebe.
Baby shower. Wow.
That so doesn't sound
like somethin' I want to do.
Later.
I can't believe
I'm gonna have a party.
[all chuckle]
This is so great!
A party! Yay!
[laughing]
Yes! Yes!
[crying]
- I don't know why.
- Oh.
This is what I've got going
for the party so far
liquor-wise.
- "Get a lot of liquor."
- Great. Great.
Okay, now, uh, in terms
of the invite list
obviously, I've got
you, me, and Chandler
and I'm gonna invite
Gunther because
well, we've been talking
about this pretty loud.
I'll be there.
Alright, and.. Oh, listen,
I know it's your party
but I'd really like
to limit the number
of museum geeks
that are gonna be there.
Yeah. Tell ya what,
let's not invite
any of the
anthropologists, okay?
Just the dinosaur dudes!
Okay! We'll need
a six-pack of Zima.
Hey, guys, what are you doing?
Oh, just planning my bachelor
party with my best man.
Yeah, well, good luck
trying to top the last one.
Yeah, see, I don't think
it's gonna be that difficult
considering this one
won't take place
in the basement
of a Pizza Hut.
"Oh, I'm Ross. I'm Ross.
I'm too good for the Hut.
I'm too good for the Hut."
Look, I gotta go pick up Ben.
Uh, everything
so far sounds great, Joey.
Just remember to keep it
on the mellow side, okay?
Just a couple of guys
hanging out playing poker
no, no strippers
or anything, okay?
- You got it.
- Okay, see you later.
See ya.
Ha-ha-ha-ha. Have fun planning
your mellow bachelor party.
Well, there's gonna
be strippers there.
He didn't say anything
about no strippers.
He just said,
"No strippers."
Oh, I chose not to hear that.
Look what I got! Look what
I got! Look what I got!
Oh.
Can you believe they make these
for little people?
Oh, little village people.
Oh. Okay.
Look at this one.
This is my favorite.
- Oh, that is so sweet!
- I know!
Phoebe is gonna love
dressing them in these!
Huh. Except, Phoebe's
not gonna be the one
who gets to dress them.
Because she's not going
to get to keep the babies.
Oh, my God!
We are throwing the most
depressing baby shower ever!
[gasps]
Wait a minute!
Unless, we give her
all gifts that she can use
after she's done
being pregnant.
Like, um, like
regular coffee, tequila!
Oh, and somebody could
get her those
those leather pants
that she's always wanted!
Oh, she's gonna love that!
What the hell is this?
What, you actually thought
it would make me feel better?
To give me something
I can't even use
for another two months?
This sucks! Ugh!
Alright, what's my next present?
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, listen, man,
about the stripper..
- Yeah?
- Good call!
Okay, a little announcement,
a little announcement.
I've decided that my best man
is my best friend Gunther!
What's my last name?
Central Perk?
Thanks for not marrying Rachel.
Oh, hey, Gunther,
don't-don't forget your shirt.
Hey, hey, what are those?
Oh, little party favors,
check it out.
- Wow! Yeah!
- 'Yeah?'
Oh, oh, oh.
Ohhh.
Okay. Okay, a little
announcement.
I just want everybody
to know that the position
of my best man is still open.
And, uh, you know, so is
the position of the bride.
- Great!
- Smooth, man.
Yeah, you got some chili
on your neck.
Well, I just want
to say, thanks everyone
this-this was great, okay.
And, hey! See you guys
Monday morning.
- Thanks, Joey.
- Hey, don't forget your shirt.
Oh, thanks!
Okay, hey, museum geeks,
party's over. Okay.
Wave bye-bye to the nice lady.
There you go.
Back to your
parents' basement. Alright.
Come on, boys, come on out!
Here you go. Alright.
Ohh, look
at the little birdies!
- Are those yours?
- Yeah.
Well, I didn't know
they let you
keep chickens and ducks as pets.
Oh, yeah, yeah. And I got
the duck totally trained too.
Watch this.
Stare at the wall.
Hardly move.
Be white.
You are really good at that.
So, uh, I had fun tonight
you throw one hell of a party.
Oh, thanks. Thanks.
Yeah, it was great meetin' ya.
And listen, if any of my friends
ever get married
or, you know
have a birthday
or a Tuesday--
Yeah, that would be great.
So, I guess, um, goodnight.
Oh, unless you, uh..
...you just wanna hang around.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'll let you play
with my duck.
[quacks]
[instrumental music]
Hey..
Stripper!
The stripper stole the ring!
Chandler, get up! Get up!
- What?
- The ring is gone!
Ugh. Okay, just a sec, gimme
a minute to wake up for this..
Ah-ha-ha.
You lost the ring!
You're the worst best man ever!
Dude, this isn't funny!
What am I gonna do?
I go to sleep last night,
everything's cool!
I wake up this morning,
the stripper's gone
and the ring is gone!
You slept with the stripper?
Of course!
- Hi, guys.
- Hi, Phoebe.
Hi, Phoebe.
I-I wanted to apologize
if I, you know
seemed a tad edgy yesterday
at my shower.
You know, it's just
the hormones, you know.
- No, we.. Hormones, yeah.
- Hormones.
Anyway, I just wanted
to say thank you
it was just,
it was so sweet.
- Oh, okay.
- It was so sweet.
Wow, you seem to be doing
so much better. That's great.
- H-how are things going?
- Good.
You know.. No, but, okay,
it's-it feels
like, everything's been
about me lately
so what's happening with you?
Oh, well, actually
we were just talking
about me not going
to Ross' wedding.
It just might be too hard,
given the history and all that..
Wow! This reminds me
of the time when I was, um
living on the street
and this guy offered
to buy me food
if I slept with him.
Well, h-how is this like that?
Well, let's see,
it's not...really like that
because you see that
was an actual problem
and, uh, yours is just like,
you know, bunch of, you know
high school crap that nobody
really gives, you know..
Well, I'm-I'm sorry,
I guess I just thought--
Alright, here comes
the water works.
Ugh! I don't know
what I'm gonna do!
I called the company that
sent her and th-they don't care.
Then I called 911
and they yelled at me
if this isn't an emergency,
then what is?
Hey, guys.
- Hey!
- Hey. Hey.
I just wanted to thank you
again for last night.
What a great party.
And the guys
from work had a blast.
You know, one of them
had never been
to a bachelor party before.
Yeah! And-and another one
had never been
to a party before, so..
So, uh, hey, that, uh,
that wedding ring, huh?
- Man, that is nice!
- Yeah, right!
Yeah, I was, uh,
I was thinkin' I might pick
one of those
babies up for myself.
Where might one
get one of those?
That ring?
When my grandmother
first came to this country
that ring and the clothes on her
back were all she had with her.
So you might say
that the ring is irreplaceable?
Oh, absolutely! It's been
in my family for generations
and every bride who has worn it
has lived a long and happy life.
So you might say,
it's a magic ring.
[both chuckle]
Yeah, the stripper stole it.
My-my ring?
My-my wedding ring?
The-the stripper
stole my wedding ring?
H-how? How-how could
this happen?
Well, I think it all
started when you said
"Hey, Joey, why don't
you be my best man?"
Alright, alright, fine! I'm
gonna-I'm gonna call the cops.
Dude, I-I screwed up,
you don't have to turn me in!
Not on you!
On the stripper!
Oh, yeah, well,
I already did that.
They said they're
gonna look into it right after
they solve all the murders.
Okay, well, then, we'll-we'll
call the company that sent her.
I did that too!
They wouldn't give me
her real name or her number.
They said, if I bothered them
again, they'd call the police.
I said, "If you talk
to the police
you tell them
I'm missin' a ring."
So what, Joey? Wh-wh-what?
What are you telling me?
That there's nothing we can do?
Well, how could this happen?
Look, Ross,
I am so, so sorry. I-I..
[slams phone]
Well, what if we just,
uh, called her
used a fake name
and had her come to my office?
Oh, that sounds like fun,
but we've got a ring to find!
[instrumental music]
Here's your tea, Phoebe.
Mm, it's so good.
[both sigh]
Oh, thanks. Sweet.
- Good.
- I'm so glad you like it.
- Oh!
- What?
What? She made the tea!
No, I-I think I just
had a contraction.
- You what?
- Oh, my God!
Yeah, I thought I felt one
a couple of minutes ago
and now I know that
definitely was one.
Oh, wait, you-you can't
have the baby here!
I mean, I haven't
sterilized the apartment
since the guys moved out!
It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
You know what? It's okay.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna
boil some water
and just rip up some sheets!
No. It's alright,
it's probably false labor.
They said that that could
happen near the end
so, just somebody
get the book.
- Rachel, get the book!
- The book! Okay! Okay!
Here.
- The Bible?
- I don't know!
[instrumental music]
Alright, okay, okay,
this is great.
Uh, Chandler,
you get behind the desk.
And-and when she comes in
hopefully, she won't
recognize you because
well, why would she?
Uh, okay, and then
you buzz Ross and I.
You be, uh, Mr. Gonzales,
and I'll be Mr. Wong.
Diverse.
[knock on door]
(female #1)
'Anybody call for security?'
You be cool.
Okay, which one of you guys
is Gunther Central Perk?
- Hey, Joey?
- Where's my ring?
My dead grandmother's wedding
ring? Where is it? Where is it?
Way to be cool, man.
What's he talking about?
There was a ring,
in a box, on my nightstand.
After you left,
it was gone!
Wait a minute, you guys think
I stole some ring?
(all)
Yeah!
We know you took it,
so just-just save yourself
the time and confess!
Okay, who are you,
The Hardy Boys?
Look, I don't need to steal
some stupid ring, alright?
I make $1600 a week
doing what I do.
Any of you guys make that?
Marry me.
What?
[instrumental music]
I don't get it.
It was in my room all night.
If she didn't take it,
and I didn't take it
and you didn't take it,
then who did?
[duck quacking]
Shh! We're trying to think.
I still don't get how you know
when it's false labor.
Well, do you see any babies?
- How do you feel?
- Okay, I guess, I mean..
I don't know, it's just..
I guess, I know it's going
to be over soon, so..
But isn't that a good thing?
I mean, you said
you were sick of this.
I know. It's just, you know
usually when you're,
when you're done
with the pregnant thing,
then you
you know, you get
to do the mom thing.
I'm gonna be,
you know, sitting around
in my leather pants,
drinking tequila.
Some moms do that.
Okay, that's even sadder.
Look, I know, I know, what I got
myself into, you know..
It's just that
now that they're in me
it's like...it's like I know
them, you know, and, and..
It's just not, it's not gonna
be easy when, you know
these little babies
have to go away.
I know, sweetie
but it's not like you're not
gonna have anything.
I mean, you're gonna
have nieces and nephews.
I mean, some ways
that's even better.
- Yeah, okay.
- No, really. Really, Pheebs.
I mean, you're not
gonna be the one
worrying about
saving for college
or yelling at them
when they're bad
you know, or deciding
to put 'em on Ritalin
when they just won't
calm down. You know?
I mean, you're gonna be
the one that they come to
when they wanna
run away from home
and the one they
talk to about sex.
And you just get
to be cool Aunt Phoebe!
Cool Aunt Phoebe.
I am pretty cool.
Oh.
Yeah. And you know what else?
Oh, my God,
are they gonna love you!
- They are gonna love me.
- Oh!
- Thanks, you guys.
- Aww.
- Oh, honey..
- Again.
Oh, sweetie.
Thanks. Oh!
- What?
- Oh, God!
- Just kidding.
- Oh.
- Ahh!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, got you again,
you're so easy.
[instrumental music]
If anything should
happen to him..
Joey! The vet said
it's a simple procedure.
So! Things could go wrong!
You don't know!
What if he doesn't make it?
- He will, Joe.
- Yeah, but what if he doesn't?
He's such a good duck.
♪ And tell me
when will our eyes meet? ♪
♪ When can I touch you? ♪
♪ When will
this strong yearning end? ♪
♪ And when will I hold you ♪
♪ Again? ♪♪
I'm just so worried
about him, you know?
- Somebody lose a ring?
- Aah!
Oh, my God! Thank you!
Thank you so much!
[sniffs]
- H-h-h-how's the duck?
- Yeah.
He's doing just fine,
he's resting now
but you can see him
in a little bit.
- Oh.
- Great.
Hey, listen, Ross, thanks
for being so cool about this.
- No, that's alright.
- No, it's not.
I mean, you-you made me
your best man
and I totally let you down!
Hey, come on,
it's not your fault.
Yeah, it is!
You wouldn't have
lost the ring, right?
You know what
Ross, you were right
from the start
he should be your best man.
No, you should.
Look, don't argue with me--
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I get to choose my best man.
I want both you guys.
- Really?
Hey, both you guys should be
up there with me.
I mean, you two are-are my..
I mean, I'm lucky
to have just one good..
Th-thanks, man.
I gotta go check
something over here.
- What a baby.
- Total wuss!
[instrumental music]
[hornpipe music]
[quacks]
[theme music]